Class of 1905 Records, 1901-1975
Smith College Archives
Class of 1905 Records
1901-1975
Smith College. Class of 1905.
RG 80 UUID:a3c4a34c-8cb6-4402-bb27-9de6fef46d40
19 boxes (10.1 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection is in 19 boxes and contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1905.
The Class of 1905 was the twenty-seventh entering class and the twenty-seventh graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1905 records, 1901-1975, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1905, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, obituaries, financial information, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1905 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Commencement 1905 (Box 1670, Folder 1)
- Commencement Photographs 1905 (Box 1670, Folder 2)
- Commencement Music 1905 (Box 1670, Folder 3)
- Descendants 1934-1965 (Box 1670, Folder 4)
- Donors to College Funds undated (Box 1670, Folder 5)
- Finances 1954-1970 (Box 1670, Folder 6)
- Freshman Grind by 1904 1901 (Box 1670, Folder 7)
- Freshman Handbook 1901 (Box 1670, Folder 8)
- Groups 1901-1905 (Box 1670, Folder 9)
- Class History undated (Box 1670, Folder 10)
- Ivy Day 1905 (Box 1670, Folder 11)
- Ivy Day Photographs 1905 (Box 1670, Folder 12)
- Junior Prom 1904 (Box 1670, Folder 13)
- Junior Ushers 1904 (Box 1670, Folder 14)
- Class Letters 1919-1975 (Box 1670, Folder 15)
- Obituaries, Clippings, Letters, etc 1905-1930 (Box 1671, Folder 1)
- Weddings, Obituaries, Press Clippings, Class Letters 1929-1957 (Box 1671, Folder 2)
- Minutes of Class Meetings 1901-1950 (Box 1672, Folder 1)
- Organization undated (Box 1672, Folder 2)
- Prayer Meetings 1905 (Box 1672, Folder 3)
- Reunions undated (Box 1672, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1908 (Box 1672, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1910 (Box 1672, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1915-1917 (Box 1672, Folder 7)
- Reunions 1920 (Box 1672, Folder 8)
- Reunions 1925 (Box 1672, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1930 (Box 1672, Folder 10)
- Reunions- Book of Our Sons 1932 (Box 1672, Folder 11)
- Reunions- Book of Our Daughters 1934 (Box 1672, Folder 12)
- Reunions 1935-1939 (Box 1672, Folder 13)
- Reunions 1940 (Box 1672, Folder 14)
- Reunions 1945 (Box 1672, Folder 15)
- Reunions 1950 (Box 1672, Folder 16)
- Reunions 1955 (Box 1673, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1960 (Box 1673, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1965 (Box 1673, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1970 (Box 1673, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1975 (Box 1673, Folder 5)
- Reunion- Mad March Hare 1927-1940 (Box 1673, Folder 6)
- Reunion Songs undated (Box 1673, Folder 7)
- Songs undated (Box 1673, Folder 8)
- Sophomore Reception 1902 (Box 1673, Folder 9)
- Class Supper 1905 (Box 1673, Folder 10)
- Senior Dramatics 1905 (Box 1674, Folder 1)
- Senior Dramatics- Photographs 1905 (Box 1674, Folder 2)
- Senior Dramatics- A.C. Bradley 1905 (Box 1674, Folder 3)
- Senior Dramatics- Groups 1905 (Box 1674, Folder 4)
- Senior Dramatics- E.T. Babcock 1905 (Box 1674, Folder 5)
- Senior Dramatics- M. Lockwood 1905 (Box 1674, Folder 6)
- Senior Dramatics- K. C. Noyles 1905 (Box 1674, Folder 7)
- Senior Dramatics- Costume Book 1905 (Box 1674, Folder 8)
- Costume, Memorabilia 1955 (Box OV)
- Class Secretary's Card File (Box OV)
- Pillowcases and Banner (Box OV)